aurasma.com 2012-10-19

# Aurasma

By downloading, installing, running, and accessing the Aurasma mobile application and corresponding Aurasma online service and related content (collectively " _Aurasma_ "), you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. Certain features of Aurasma may require you become an Aurasma member, which, as part of the registration process, may require that you provide us with certain personal information. Your use of Aurasma is subject to this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into the Terms of Service that you accepted by downloading the Aurasma mobile application to your mobile device or by accessing Aurasma. The Terms of Services can be found on our website, for reference.

In this Privacy Policy, "you", "your", "yours", and their derivations, are used to refer to you, the Aurasma user. "We", "us", and "our", and their derivations, are used to refer to _Aurasma, Inc._ , if you are a user located in North America or South America, or to _Aurasma Systems Limited_ (Registration No. 3175909), if you are a user located outside of North America and South America.

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you how and in what context we may collect certain personal or non-public information from you, and, further, how we use and protect the information we collect.

**Collection and Use.** When you download the Aurasma mobile application and/or when you use Aurasma, we may collect and store some or all of the following:

  * Device information and sign-on data (including device ID).
  * Your name
  * Your email address
  * Location data
  * Your preferred language, currency, and country site
  * Information about how you interact with the Aurasma mobile application, the Aurasma service, and any sites, locales, events, or other happenings we make available through the service.

We may use all or any portion of the information we collect: (i) to provide you and other users with access to and use of Aurasma, (ii) to identify and deliver content to your mobile device, (iii) to provide you with applicable, periodic software updates, (iv) to personalize your Aurasma experience, and/or (v) to operate and improve Aurasma, including, without limitation, the mobile application(s), content delivery systems, servers, sites, services, and tools.

**Social Networking.** Aurasma may include or utilize social networking or "share functionality" or may contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for, any share functionality or the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party site. You are subject to the policies of those third parties where applicable. By using Aurasma, you expressly relieve us from any and all liability arising from your use of any share functionality or third-party site accessed from the mobile application. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to anyone.

**User Control and Uninstall.** You can access and change user settings or delete your account and/or account information from within Aurasma and from the options/settings menu on your mobile device. Methods of uninstalling our mobile application vary depending on your mobile device. To uninstall the Aurasma mobile application, please use the application manager provided with your device or consult your device manual for reference.

**Security.** The information we collect may be stored locally on your device and may be transmitted to our servers in the United States and/or European Union. The transmission of information over wireless and wired networks is not inherently secure. We use many tools to help protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure; however we do not guarantee, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private when using Aurasma.

**Policy Changes.** We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time in our discretion. A material change to this Privacy Policy will take effect (i) immediately for new Aurasma users, or (ii) 30 days after we provide notice of the change for existing Aurasma users. We provide notice of changes to this Privacy Policy by publishing revised versions of this Privacy Policy on this publicly-available website and/or on other publicly-available websites. If you do not agree with any change we make to this Privacy Policy, you should immediately cease all use of Aurasma and uninstall and permanently delete the Aurasma mobile application from your mobile device(s). Retaining the Aurasma mobile application or accessing any part of Aurasma after the 30-day period has expired will constitute your irrevocable acceptance of any changes.

**Contact Information.** For questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at "Aurasma Legal - Global Privacy Practices" using the appropriate address listed below:

_For North American or South American users:_

Aurasma, Inc.  
One Market Plaza  
Spear Tower, 19th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94105  
USA  
+1 415 243-9955  

_For other users:_

Aurasma Systems Limited  
Autonomy House  
Cambridge Business Park  
Cowley Rd.  
Cambridge  
CB4 0WZ  
United Kingdom  
+44 1223 448000  

_Effective June 1, 2011_
